<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>words on frizzande</title>
    <link>https://frizzande.io/words/</link>
    <description>Recent content in words on frizzande</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://frizzande.io/words/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>adam and the eaves</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/adam_and_the_eaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/adam_and_the_eaves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;the first time we ever benched, we were working nights as a delivery driver.&#xA;we had such soreness in our chest that we needed to adjust to driving underhanded because we were absolutely incapable of lifting our arms to our chest.&#xA;truthfully, at times is was an effort to carry a bag full of food from our car to knock on their front door.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we will call our first gym partner Adam.&#xA;Adam was a sprinter, a rugby player, a natural athlete and the school sports captain when were in high school together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pro nouns</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/pro_nouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/pro_nouns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;we prefer &amp;rsquo;they/them&#39;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we prefer the third person plural as we believe that we are more than one person&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we are typing these letters into a computer keyboard&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and we are reading these words on our website&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the plurality of our singularity&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>thirty two</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/thirty_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/thirty_two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;this piece originated from a prompt: a birthday letter from us at 32 to our future present self - and yet, we found an obstruction, a blockage, as traditionally (previously) the birthday letter would be exchanged with one from MADDY, whom we have sadly not encountered for a hot minute. sunshine and turtles going out to you, homeslice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and so, what follows is a treatise on &lt;strong&gt;THE HAIR CRISIS&lt;/strong&gt;, and how it came to be &lt;strong&gt;THE HERE CRISES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>recover</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/recover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/recover/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;when you have had to make big, adult life decisions, how have you known if you made the right choice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;perhaps a better phrasing would have been: &lt;strong&gt;how have you known when you have made a mistake?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we think, now, that the judgment ex post facto is irrelevant; that what matters is making a choice at all&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(you, we, me) made a plan, sketched the outlines, the paths ahead, and at some point - this point, now - you realise that it&amp;rsquo;s the wrong plan for the time. the plan is still solid (we hope); it&amp;rsquo;s true to me, from then; it&amp;rsquo;s true to who i want to be; and it gives back to the communities and networks that have supported me to this point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>four fish, five eyes</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/four_fish_five_eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/four_fish_five_eyes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;09,30 qf129 to shanghai&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;07,30 international airport&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;07,00 depart the btm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;05,59 awake&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we made it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we had a goal, a dream: to play nationals with bench.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but we are also arrogant; we are vain; we are our own ego, maniac.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we missed brunch, we missed lunch, we missed kaf in the between.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;there&amp;rsquo;s a speed, a pace, a height - an energy, with opens, that we&amp;rsquo;ve missed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;we had a choice: split or mixed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the living dead</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/the_living_dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/the_living_dead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t remember when I wrote this piece. It came from a dark place, twelve levels underwater, with no light coming through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please keep a friend nearby to help pull you back up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I am already dead.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My life, of late, has been suffocatingly dark.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been to work for some months. The Monday, the first day of the last week, I went in. I had a panic attack in the lab, and I left. I went home and tried to breathe. The Tuesday, the second day of the last week, I had a panic attack in the lift, and I left. I went home and tried to breathe. The Wednesday, the third day of the last week, I thought about having a panic attack, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t breathe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowing Smoke</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/blowing_smoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/blowing_smoke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I enjoy breathing smoke, and feeling where it flows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some number of people have never smoked a cigarette. It&amp;rsquo;s a thing that you only need to try once, but likely should not. They will not die from their last cigarette, and neither will I.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I see time differently to most people. I see time as the here, the now, and nothing beyond tomorrow. Nothing beyond tomorrow, because tomorrow never comes for me. I panic about tomorrow, panic that it will come back. It&amp;rsquo;s already back.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What To Do When You Can&#39;t Play Ultimate</title>
      <link>https://frizzande.io/words/what_to_do_when_you_cant_play_ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://frizzande.io/words/what_to_do_when_you_cant_play_ultimate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People have asked me where I&amp;rsquo;ve been. They&amp;rsquo;ve noticed I&amp;rsquo;m not in any of the photos of Bench in Hawaii, and that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t at Eastern Regionals two weekends ago. I&amp;rsquo;m okay, but i didn&amp;rsquo;t feel up to flying to Kaimana or driving to Canberra.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;February was a month for me, and really it was a month after a couple of other months. I&amp;rsquo;m a big disc nerd; I love friz. The high of friends + running has always been a solid foundation when other things haven&amp;rsquo;t been going so well. I missed a couple of Brunches with the boys, which was disappointing, even if I think it was the right choice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
